Guide to the Ship Scalers, Dry Dock, and Boat Yard Workers Union, Local 541 (Seattle, Washington) Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Ship Scalers, Dry Dock, and Boat Yard Workers Union, Local 541 (Seattle, Washington) Records, 1939-1991; 4571-001; 16 cubic feet 16 boxes
  - Series VII: Member Files, 1944-1986 (Box-folder 12/1-12/44; 16/9; 12/45-14/246)
    - Subseries B: Member Files: A-Z, 1944-1986 (Box-folder 12/45-14/220)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with I, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 13/116)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with J, 1982 (Box-folder 13/118)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with J, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 13/119)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with J, 1982 (Box-folder 13/120)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with J, 1984 (Box-folder 13/121)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with J, 1983 (Box-folder 13/122)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with J, 1983 (Box-folder 13/123)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with J, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 13/124)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with J, 1984 (Box-folder 13/125)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with J, 1983 (Box-folder 13/126)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with J, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 13/127)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with J, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 13/128)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with J, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 13/129)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with J, 1978-1985 (Box-folder 13/130)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with J, 1981 (Box-folder 13/131)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with J, 1979 (Box-folder 13/132)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with J, 1982 (Box-folder 13/133)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with J, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 13/134)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with J, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 13/135)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with J, 1980 (Box-folder 13/136)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with J, 1984 (Box-folder 13/137)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with J, 1984 (Box-folder 13/138)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with J, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 13/139)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with J, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 13/140)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with J, 1980 (Box-folder 13/141)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with J, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 13/142)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with J, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 13/117)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with K, 1982 (Box-folder 13/143)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with K, 1980 (Box-folder 13/144)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with K, 1981 (Box-folder 13/145)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with K, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 13/146)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with K, 1980 (Box-folder 13/147)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with K, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 13/148)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with K, 1982 (Box-folder 13/149)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with K, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 13/150)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with K, 1981 (Box-folder 13/151)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with K, 1983 (Box-folder 13/152)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with K, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 13/153)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with K, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 13/154)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with K, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 13/155)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with K, 1982 (Box-folder 13/156)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with K, 1984 (Box-folder 13/157)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with K, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 13/158)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with K, 1982 (Box-folder 13/159)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with K, 1974-1981 (Box-folder 13/160)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with K, 1984 (Box-folder 13/161)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with K, 1983 (Box-folder 13/162)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with K, 1980 (Box-folder 13/163)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with L, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 13/164)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with L, 1968-1986 (Box-folder 13/165)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with L, 1983 (Box-folder 13/166)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with L, 1980 (Box-folder 13/167)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with L, 1982 (Box-folder 13/168)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with L, 1986 (Box-folder 13/169)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with L, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 13/170)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with L, 1981 (Box-folder 13/171)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with L, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 13/172)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with L, 1982 (Box-folder 13/173)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with L, 1983 (Box-folder 13/174)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with L, 1981 (Box-folder 13/175)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with L, 1982 (Box-folder 13/176)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with L, 1981 (Box-folder 13/177)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with L, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 13/178)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with L, 1983 (Box-folder 13/179)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with L, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 13/180)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with L, 1980 (Box-folder 13/181)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with L, 1980-1985 (Box-folder 13/182)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with L, 1981 (Box-folder 13/183)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with L, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 13/184)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with L, 1980 (Box-folder 13/185)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 13/187)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1985 (Box-folder 13/188)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1981 (Box-folder 13/189)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1978 (Box-folder 13/190)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 13/191)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1979 (Box-folder 13/192)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1985 (Box-folder 13/193)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1983 (Box-folder 13/194)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1986 (Box-folder 13/195)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1982 (Box-folder 13/196)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1982 (Box-folder 13/197)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 13/198)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1983 (Box-folder 13/199)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 13/200)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 13/201)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 13/202)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 13/203)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1981 (Box-folder 13/204)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 13/205)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 13/206)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 13/207)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1981 (Box-folder 13/208)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 13/209)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 13/210)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 13/211)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 13/212)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 13/213)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1983 (Box-folder 13/214)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1982 (Box-folder 13/215)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 13/216)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 13/217)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 13/218)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1982 (Box-folder 13/219)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with M, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 13/186)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with Mc, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 14/1)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with Mc, 1977-1985 (Box-folder 14/2)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with Mc, 1983-1983 (Box-folder 14/3)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with Mc, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 14/4)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with Mc, 1983 (Box-folder 14/5)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with Mc, 1982 (Box-folder 14/6)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with Mc, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 14/7)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with Mc, 1980 (Box-folder 14/8)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with Mc, 1983 (Box-folder 14/9)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with Mc, 1981 (Box-folder 14/10)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with Mc, 1983 (Box-folder 14/11)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with Mc, 1982 (Box-folder 14/12)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with Mc, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 14/13)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with Mc, 1978-1986 (Box-folder 14/14)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with N, 1983 (Box-folder 14/15)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with N, 1978 (Box-folder 14/16)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with N, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 14/17)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with N, 1981 (Box-folder 14/18)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with O, 1980 (Box-folder 14/19)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with O, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 14/20)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with O, 1981 (Box-folder 14/21)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with O, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 14/22)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with O, 1981 (Box-folder 14/23)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with O, 1980 (Box-folder 14/24)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with P, 1981 (Box-folder 14/25)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with P, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 14/26)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with P, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 14/27)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with P, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 14/28)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with P, 1983 (Box-folder 14/29)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with P, 1983 (Box-folder 14/30)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with P, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 14/31)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with P, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 14/32)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with P, 1983 (Box-folder 14/33)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with P, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 14/34)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with P, 1982 (Box-folder 14/35)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with P, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 14/36)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with P, 1983 (Box-folder 14/37)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with P, 1982 (Box-folder 14/38)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with P, 1982 (Box-folder 14/39)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with P, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 14/40)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with P, 1984 (Box-folder 14/41)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with P, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 14/42)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with P, 1981 (Box-folder 14/43)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with P, 1980 (Box-folder 14/44)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with P, 1981 (Box-folder 14/45)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with Q, 1982 (Box-folder 14/46)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1985 (Box-folder 14/47)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 14/48)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1981 (Box-folder 14/49)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 14/50)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 14/51)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1982 (Box-folder 14/52)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1982 (Box-folder 14/53)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 14/54)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 14/55)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 14/56)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 14/57)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1983 (Box-folder 14/58)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1972 (Box-folder 14/59)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1985 (Box-folder 14/60)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1944-1986 (Box-folder 14/61)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 14/62)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1981 (Box-folder 14/63)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1982 (Box-folder 14/64)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1982 (Box-folder 14/65)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 14/66)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 14/67)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 14/68)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1979 (Box-folder 14/69)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1982 (Box-folder 14/70)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1983 (Box-folder 14/71)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1981 (Box-folder 14/72)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1982 (Box-folder 14/73)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 14/74)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1982 (Box-folder 14/75)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 14/76)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 14/77)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 14/78)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1981 (Box-folder 14/79)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 14/80)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1980 (Box-folder 14/81)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1982 (Box-folder 14/82)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 14/83)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with R, 1978 (Box-folder 14/84)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 14/85)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1982 (Box-folder 14/86)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 14/87)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1980 (Box-folder 14/88)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1982 (Box-folder 14/89)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 14/90)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 14/91)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1980-1985 (Box-folder 14/92)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1984 (Box-folder 14/93)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1982 (Box-folder 14/94)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1984 (Box-folder 14/95)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 14/96)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 14/97)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 14/98)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 14/99)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 14/100)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1985 (Box-folder 14/101)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 14/102)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1983 (Box-folder 14/103)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 14/104)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1980 (Box-folder 14/105)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1980 (Box-folder 14/106)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 14/107)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 14/108)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1983 (Box-folder 14/109)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1982 (Box-folder 14/110)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 14/111)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 14/112)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 14/113)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1982 (Box-folder 14/114)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 14/115)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1981 (Box-folder 14/116)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1982 (Box-folder 14/117)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 14/118)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1984 (Box-folder 14/119)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1978 (Box-folder 14/120)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 14/121)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1957-1982 (Box-folder 14/122)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1982 (Box-folder 14/123)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1983 (Box-folder 14/124)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1981 (Box-folder 14/125)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1981 (Box-folder 14/126)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 14/127)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with S, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 14/128)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 14/129)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1981 (Box-folder 14/130)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1985 (Box-folder 14/131)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 14/132)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 14/133)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 14/134)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 14/135)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1981-1981 (Box-folder 14/136)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1982 (Box-folder 14/137)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 14/138)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1980 (Box-folder 14/139)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 14/140)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1981 (Box-folder 14/141)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1980 (Box-folder 14/142)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 14/143)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 14/144)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1979 (Box-folder 14/145)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1982 (Box-folder 14/146)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1980 (Box-folder 14/147)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1980 (Box-folder 14/148)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1981 (Box-folder 14/149)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1980 (Box-folder 14/150)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1981 (Box-folder 14/151)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 14/152)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1982 (Box-folder 14/153)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1975-1985 (Box-folder 14/154)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1980 (Box-folder 14/155)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 14/156)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with T, 1982 (Box-folder 14/157)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with U, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 14/158)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with V, 1984 (Box-folder 14/159)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with V, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 14/160)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with V, 1983 (Box-folder 14/161)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with V, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 14/162)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1982 (Box-folder 14/163)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1980 (Box-folder 14/164)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 14/165)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1984 (Box-folder 14/166)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 14/167)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1980-1985 (Box-folder 14/168)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1980-1985 (Box-folder 14/169)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 14/170)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 14/171)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 14/172)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 14/173)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 14/174)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1982-1982 (Box-folder 14/175)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1977-1985 (Box-folder 14/176)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1984 (Box-folder 14/177)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 14/178)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 14/179)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1984 (Box-folder 14/180)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 14/181)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1982 (Box-folder 14/182)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1980 (Box-folder 14/183)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1983 (Box-folder 14/184)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1981 (Box-folder 14/185)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1983 (Box-folder 14/186)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1981 (Box-folder 14/187)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1983 (Box-folder 14/188)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1978 (Box-folder 14/189)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 14/190)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1981 (Box-folder 14/191)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1981 (Box-folder 14/192)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1981 (Box-folder 14/193)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1980 (Box-folder 14/194)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1982 (Box-folder 14/195)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1982 (Box-folder 14/196)
      - Member Files: Last Names Beginning with W, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 14/197)